<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KotlinApp</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="microphone">Microphone</string>
    
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_content">Qovo – Terms and Conditions\n\nLast updated: 21/09/2025\n\nWelcome to Qovo. These Terms and Conditions govern your use of the Qovo mobile application and its related services. By accessing or using the Qovo mobile app, you agree to be bound by these Terms.\n\n1. Definitions\n• User means any person who creates an account on the Qovo app.\n• Renter means a User who books a vehicle through the Qovo app.\n• Owner means a User who lists a vehicle for rent on the Qovo app.\n• Vehicle means any car or automobile made available for rental through the Qovo app.\n\n2. Eligibility\n• Users must be at least 21 years old.\n• Renters must hold a valid driver\'s license.\n• By using the Qovo app, you confirm that all information you provide is accurate.\n\n3. Account Registration\n• You must provide accurate, current, and complete information.\n• You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account.\n• You must notify us immediately of any unauthorized use.\n\n4. Vehicle Rental\n• Vehicle availability is subject to owner approval.\n• Renters are responsible for returning vehicles in the same condition.\n• Additional fees may apply for late returns or damage.\n\n5. Payment Terms\n• All payments are processed securely through our platform.\n• Rental fees and applicable taxes will be clearly displayed.\n• Refunds are subject to our cancellation policy.\n\n6. User Conduct\n• Users must comply with all applicable laws.\n• Prohibited activities include driving under the influence.\n• Violation of these terms may result in account suspension.\n\n7. Insurance and Liability\n• Basic insurance coverage is included with all rentals.\n• Users are responsible for any damages not covered by insurance.\n\n8. Privacy and Data Protection\n• We collect and use your information as described in our Privacy Policy.\n• Your data is protected according to industry standards.\n\n9. Termination\n• Either party may terminate this agreement at any time.\n• We reserve the right to suspend accounts for violations.\n\n10. Changes to Terms\n• We may update these Terms from time to time.\n• Continued use constitutes acceptance of new terms.\n\n11. Contact Information\n• For questions about these Terms, contact us at support@qovo.com\n\nBy using Qovo, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions.</string>

    <string name="profile_picture">Profile picture</string>

    <!-- Encabezado (si quieres sacar del layout literal) -->
    <string name="user_name_example">Juan Pablo Baron</string>
    <string name="user_phone_example">3152403373</string>
    <string name="user_email_example">juanpa.baron18@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="logo_wordmark">QOVO</string>

    <!-- Botones principales -->
    <string name="add_car">Add Car</string>
    <string name="visited_places">Visited Places</string>
    <string name="communications">Communications</string>
    <string name="payment">Payment</string>

    <!-- Botones inferiores -->
    <string name="switch_account">Switch Account</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go Back</string>
</resources>